ICS Lambert has announced their Q4
results and let's check it out how they
performed for this quarter and here the
company has declared a final dividend of
rupees 7 per share and the record date
will be announced in the AGM
meeting and here all the figures were
given in lakhs and to begin with the
total income made by the company here
clearly yearon year we could see a
pretty decent improvement from 5,165
crores it went down to
5,851 crores
But quarteron quarter a slight marginal
decline can be
seen and here the gross
premium returns has been increased from
6,474 crores to 6,93 crores. And when it
comes to the expenses part in the
expenses were increased year on year and
quarter and quarter from 4,693 crores it
went on to
5,4 35 crores and even quarter and
quarter also the same kind of an
improvement has been seen in terms of
expenses made by the
company and when it comes to the net
profit or pat made by the company here
both yearon year and quarteron quarter
we could see a decline especially
quarter and quarter from 742 crores.
Sorry 724 crores it went down to 59
crores but quarter year on year we could
see a marginal decline. Overall the net
profit has been impacted year on year
and quarter on quarter by the company
and this will definitely have an impact
on the earnings per share. The diluted
EPS stood at 10.47 last year and has
slightly decreased to 10.20 20 and even
further more decline can be seen
quarteron quarter from 14.48 crores it
went down to 10.20 crores. Overall the
company's performance for this quarter
is little disappointing in terms of net
profit and even the
EPS whereas the revenues were slightly
increased yearon year. And this is all
about Lombot General Insurance Company
Limited. Thank you for watching.